Brian Ston in the draft room with newly
ressigned Trayvon Walker.
Congratulations. What a blessing on
Easter weekend.
>> 100% beyond blessed. Uh God God without
God, it wouldn't have been none of this.
And uh like to thank the everybody in
the front office from the coaches to to
everybody, man. It's it's mindblowing. I
wouldn't want to be nowhere else.
>> I was going to say, what does it mean to
you to resign with a franchise that
you've only ever known in your
professional career to know that you'll
be here?
>> It really means a lot. Uh, it just goes
to say for me, I always wanted to be
here. Like you said too, I was drafted
here as well. So, this is all I know. I
feel like a lot of my blood, sweat, and
tears that I put into this is to help
kind of get this organization with along
with other players as well to get this
organization where we want to go in the
future, which is the Super Bowl, and
that's something that I'm I really want
to help bring to this city. I feel like
that'll be major.
>> What does it say to you that last two
years they've gotten Trev uh Trevor
Dunn, uh Josh Dunn, now you're part of
that fold. They're building a new
stadium. They've got a new office
building. This whole thing has been
under construction. And to be a part of
that,
>> uh, it really means a lot to be a part
of that. Like you said, like you said,
really with the stadium, it makes a lot
of sense, too, cuz we've, this team has
just been getting better and better as
ever since I've been here. And you see
the foundation being poured into that
stadium. It's it's similar to what the
players are bringing into this building,
the coaching staff is bringing into this
building, the guys in the front office.
So you can tell everything the
trajectory of what we want here in
Jacksonville is everything's going in
the right trajectory.
>> You got it out last season. First the
wrist in San Francisco, then the knee
injury that you suffered against the
Chargers. How do you feel now? What is
your prognosis for the offseason
program?
>> Feel pretty good. Uh this offseason I
just been working on my strength with my
wrist and getting my my range of motion
back. Uh like I said, I feel healthy
now. Uh I'm ready to go, man. Got this
got this done and now I'm ready to get
back out there on the field with the
guys and get to work. And this defense
took a massive step forward last year
under coach Campanily. What are your
expectations for where you're headed
this year?
>> Uh just to continually grow from picking
up where we left off last year. Uh no no
drop off. We just want to continually
get better 1% every day. You know,
that's the motto and uh that's what
we're going to do. Uh it's no we can't
it's no going backwards.
>> First season under Liam Cohen from 4 and
13 the year before to 13 and four. What
does success look like for this team
going forward? I think for us it's just
continuously to like I said just
continuously to build off of what we've
been doing. Uh it's we don't have to go
out doing too much search and things of
that nature in my opinion. I just feel
like we keep building on the things that
we've started to implement into this
organization and I feel like we'll be
perfectly fine. Just keep believing
within each other and buying in long as
we buy in everybody we all have the same
goal in the end and that's to win games
and we know the end goal which is Super
Bowl and everything else take care take
care of itself. What did Tony Belli or
James Gladstone or Liam Cohen say to you
when they got this deal done? They they
talked to the media, Trayvon, about you
being a big part of the Jaguars DNA.
What conversations did you have with
them leading up to this?
>> We had so we uh my only time I really
really had a conversation with them was
my ex and meeting uh conversation and
all of them was just like they really
want me to get to that point to where
it's just pure dominance. they know I
have it in me and uh that's something I
love I love hearing that coming from
them them and uh it holds me to a high
standard which I really like that they
going to stay on me stay coaching me
hard and it's not just one of those
things to where obviously it's the NFL
you don't get a lot of coaching or a lot
of talks from a lot of your staff
members but that's how you know that
they really care and u man it's it's
been a journey uh it was a long journey
but we're here we came to agreement and
I'm happy for that
>> let's end with this uh Your family
surrounded you here as you signed this
contract today. Your family is big and
an important part of your life. What did
it mean to you today to have all of them
present?
>> Uh it really means a lot to me. Uh
family is everything to me. Um it's God
first and me and my family. Without my
family, I wouldn't even be in this
position. Uh to be able to be this
athlete that I am from genetics to how
they raised me. It really means a lot.
And just to have them surrounding me,
man, like I have my younger niece here.
I really wanted her here just so she
can, you know, be a part and see things
like this cuz she plays sports as well.
and not just my niece, but my mom. I
know she's proud of my dad and my
sisters as well. They put a lot of hard
work into the development of me as well
outside of the field. Congratulations,
sir. Thank you.